// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Who was Sudha Chandran",
    answer: "A dancer",
    options: [
        "A dancer",
        "A singer",
        "A writer",
        "A physicist",
        
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "what was her main problem in dancing",
    answer: "her broken leg",
    options: [
      "her broken hand",
      "her broken leg",
      "her deafness",
      "her blindness",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "How did she hurt her leg",
    answer: "She hurt her leg in a road accident",
    options: [
        "She hurt her while dancing on the stage",
        "She hurt her leg in a road accident",
        "She hurt her leg while hiking",
        "She hurt her leg while playing football",
    ]
  },
  {
  numb: 4,
  question: "in which year did her accident occur",
  answer: "In 1981",
  options: [
    "In 1997",
    "In 1984",
    "In 1981",
    "In 1990",
  ]
},
{
numb: 5,
question: "what was her inspiration as told my Ms sudha",
answer: "her failures",
options: [
  "her achievements",
  "her parents",
  "her dance teacher",
  "her failures",
]
},
    {
    numb: 6,
    question: "Stephen Hawking was a..... ",
    answer: "physicist",
    options: [
        "astrobiologist",
        "physicist",
        "Bacteriologist",
        "guitarist",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 7,
    question: "in which year did Stephen Hawking left this world",
    answer: "2018",
    options: [
      "2018",
      "1999",
      "1997",
      "2008",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "through whcih diorder was Stephen Hawking suffering?",
    answer: "neurogenic paralysis",
    options: [
      "Dementia",
      "Bipolar disorder",
      "neurogenic paralysis",
      "Schizophrenia ",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "what was the full name of Stephen Hawking",
    answer: "Stephen William Hawking",
    options: [
      "Stephen adams Hawking",
      "Stephen William Hawking",
      "Stephen Hawking jhoe",
      "Stephen Hawking aderson",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "what were the greatest doscoveries of stephen hawking",
    answer: "Discovery of Black Hole Dynamics and Gravitational Singularity",
    options: [
      "Discovery of light bulb and gravity",
      "Discovery of Black Hole Dynamics and Gravitational Singularity",
      "Discovery of atom",
      "Discovery of motor",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 11,
    question: "through whcih diorder was Helen Keller suffering?",
    answer: "blindness and deafness",
    options: [
      "blindness",
      "dumbness",
      "blindness and deafness",
      "deafness",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 12,
    question: "how did she lost her sense of hearing and sight",
    answer: "she lost her sight and hearing after a bout of illness",
    options: [
      "she lost her sight and hearing after an accident",
      "she didn't have sense of hearing and sight from birth",
      "she lost her sight and hearing in an operation",
      "she lost her sight and hearing after a bout of illness",,
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 13,
    question: "how did she listen people deaf and blind",
    answer: "she put her thumb on the speaker's lips and understand him",
    options: [
      "she put her thumb on the speaker's lips and understand him",
      "by using a machine",
      "the speaker used to wright words on her back",
      "by seeing the speaker's lips",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 14,
    question: "Helen Keller was he firt deaf blind person to...",
    answer: "earn a bachelor's degree",
    options: [
      "earn a PHD",
      "earn a master's degree",
      "earn a bachelor's degree",
      "earn a Honors in English",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 15,
    question: "what was the full name of Helen Keller",
    answer: "Helen Adams Keller",
    options: [
      "Helen Keller wilson",
      "Helen Adams Keller",
      "Helen fisk Keller",
      "Helen williams Keller",
    ]
  },
  // you can uncomment the below codes and make duplicate as more as you want to add question
  // but remember you need to give the numb value serialize like 1,2,3,5,6,7,8,9.....

  //   {
  //   numb: 6,
  //   question: "Your Question is Here",
  //   answer: "Correct answer of the question is here",
  //   options: [
  //     "Option 1",
  //     "option 2",
  //     "option 3",
  //     "option 4"
  //   ]
  // },
];